{
  "LevelId": 57,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 577,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "HYDROMETER",
      "question": "instrument is commonly used to measure the specific gravity or density of a liquid,"
    },
    {
      "id": 578,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "CHECKBOXES",
      "question": "elements in forms or digital interfaces allow users to select or mark items from a list,"
    },
    {
      "id": 579,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "PASSAMEZZO",
      "question": "lively and stylized dance in triple meter, popular during the Renaissance period,"
    },
    {
      "id": 580,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BUTTERMILK",
      "question": "sour liquid often used in cooking and baking"
    },
    {
      "id": 581,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "CHICKENPOX",
      "question": "viral infection, characterized by an itchy rash of red spots,"
    },
    {
      "id": 582,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BANDAGINGS",
      "question": "the process of applying strips or layers of material, typically cloth or gauze,"
    },
    {
      "id": 583,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BEACHBALLS",
      "question": "tossed around or bounced during recreational activities at the beach"
    },
    {
      "id": 584,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "ASTRONOMER",
      "question": "profession involves the study of celestial bodies, such as stars, planets, and galaxies,"
    },
    {
      "id": 585,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BRICKYARDS",
      "question": "term is used to describe locations or facilities where clay or shale is molded and baked"
    },
    {
      "id": 586,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BIOGRAPHER",
      "question": "occupation involves the detailed documentation and analysis of a person's life,"
    },
    {
      "id": 587,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BANDMASTER",
      "question": "leader or conductor of a musical band,"
    },
    {
      "id": 588,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "DESTINATION",
      "question": "predetermined endpoint or location to which someone or something is headed or traveling"
    }
  ]
}